Finding aid for Blanchard Family Papers, ca. 1835-ca. 2000
Bentley Historical Library
- Nathan A. Cobb
  - Visual Materials
    - Negatives, glass plate
      - 3" by 4", circa 1890-1910
        - Boats, 17 negatives (Box 10)
        - Boat's crew, Honolulu (Box 10)
        - Bong Bong, New South Wales, Australia
          (location where Cobb carried out extensive research on the host-parasite relations of the sheep liver fluke)
          - General, 2 negatives (Box 10)
          - Cattle, 3 negatives (Box 10)
          - Dancing scene, 3 negatives (Box 10)
          - Laboratory, 5 negatives (Box 11)
          - Lambs, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Station, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Bowenfels, New South Wales, Australia
          - General, 3 negatives (Box 11)
          - Bridge (Box 11)
          - Children (Box 11)
          - Picnic Party (Box 11)
        - Brisbane, Queensland, Australia
          - Near the Shelton's (Box 11)
          - Old windmill (near the Shelton's) (Box 11)
          - Queen Street, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - River (Box 11)
          - River, near the Shelton's (Box 11)
        - Bruce, Mr. (Box 11)
        - Bundaberg, Queensland, Australia
          - General (Box 11)
          - Burnett River, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Picnic Party, 3 negatives (Box 11)
          - Sugar Mill (Box 11)
          - Tourist Group (Box 11)
        - Burlington Route, Chicago to San Francisco, 7 negatives (Box 11)
        - Cabbage Palm Scrub, between Tweed and Richmond Rivers (Box 11)
        - Camp Merritt: San Francisco, California
          (military camp used during Spanish-American War to hold troops awaiting transport to the Philippines)
          - General View (Box 11)
          - Mess, 3 negatives (Box 11)
          - Troops in column, resting (Box 11)
          - Troops in column with mounted officers, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Troops marching, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Camping Trip to Warwick, California; Proctor Smoking & Reading; Horse Eating Oats (Box 11)
        - Canyon: Colorado (Box 11)
        - Cape Byron, New South Wales, Australia (Box 11)
        - Cattle dip: Fort Worth, Texas, 3 negatives (Box 11)
        - Cattle scrub, Queensland, Australia: between Brisbane and Tweed Heads from Railway Train (Box 11)
        - Cement irrigation flurries and view of San Bernardino Valley from Smiley Hts., 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Chestnut Tree: Barre, Massachusetts (Box 11)
        - Chicago and Northwest Railroad Engine (Box 11)
        - Children (two) on railroad tracks (unidentified) (Box 11)
        - Cobb family
          - "Budding Naturalist" (Victor or Roger) (Box 11)
          - Children
            - Frieda, Ruth, and Dorothy on piazza at the farm (Box 11)
            - "Frieda, Ruth and Dorry": group portraits, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Dorothy, 6 negatives (Box 11)
          - Family, general, 6 negatives (Box 11)
          - Family, canoeing at Lake Quinsigamond near Worcester, Massachusetts, 4 negatives (Box 11)
          - Family portrait at the Bigelow Place (Box 11)
          - Frieda, 6 negatives (Box 11)
          - Margaret (Box 11)
          - Nathan A.
            - 30 Maynard Street, Worcester, Massachusetts (Box 11)
            - Gum tree, in (Box 11)
            - Laboratory, in (Box 11)
            - Multiple images on one negative (Box 11)
          - Roger, 6 negatives (Box 11)
          - Ruth, 5 negatives (Box 11)
          - Victor, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Cockatoos, Moana (Box 11)
        - Combined Harvester (Box 11)
        - Convict Ship "Success" (Australia) (Box 11)
        - Corrugated iron arch: Haslev, Denmark (Box 11)
        - Cows
          - Lying (Box 11)
          - Standing in water (Box 11)
        - Creamery: Alnarp, Sweden (Box 11)
        - Curve of temperature (chart) for Jacksonville and Palmer Island, Florida (Box 11)
        - Dairy country (near Lismore, New South Wales, Australia), 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Dalrymple Farms: Carrollton, North Dakota (Box 11)
        - Deer, spotted (Box 11)
        - Denmark
          - General (Box 11)
          - American professors at Danish farmhouse (Box 11)
            (cracked)
          - Canal: Copenhagen (Box 11)
          - Cow stable in Odense (Box 11)
          - Farmhouse, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Farm scenes, 3 negatives (Box 11)
          - Horse power: Odense (Box 11)
          - Malmo, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Market: Copenhagen, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Pork packery: Haslev, 2 negatives (Box 11)
          - Seaport (Box 11)
          - Waterfront: Copenhagen, 3 negatives (Box 11)
        - Denny, Joe (youth), 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Denver, Colorado, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Devil's Canyon, Arizona (Box 12)
        - Diplosis
          - Cross section (Box 12)
          - Longitudinal section (Box 12)
        - Dredge and fish tank: Fish Commission (Box 12)
        - El Capistrano, Mission (Box 12)
          (double image)
        - Electric line repairer and Denver street scene (Box 12)
        - Electric railway (showing 60 foot rails and steel cross ties), 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Electric train line repair (Box 12)
        - Elevators (grain)
          - Florida (Box 12)
          - Galveston, Texas (Box 12)
          - Liverpool, England, 3 negatives (Box 12)
          - Ortonville to St. Paul, 5 negatives (Box 12)
          - Seattle to Tacoma (Box 12)
          - Waco, Texas (Box 12)
        - English farm scenes, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Eucalyptus trees: Alhambra, Cal. (Box 12)
        - Experiment Stations
          - Dormstadt, 3 negatives (Box 12)
          - Halle (Box 12)
        - Fargo, North Dakota (wheat fields) (Box 12)
        - Farm Scenes
          - Middle Algiers, 2 negatives (Box 12)
          - Northern France, 3 negatives (Box 12)
          - Normandy, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Farrer, William (Box 12)
        - Ferry boat: California (Box 12)
        - Fish Hawk (boat) (Box 12)
        - Flies, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Florida (native vegetation), 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Fort Worth, Texas, 7 negatives (Box 12)
        - Foster Bisco place (Box 12)
        - France (off Marseilles), 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Fresno, California (Box 12)
        - Frozen orange orchards: Orlando, Florida, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Fruit drying: San Jose, California, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Fruit Wagon, California (Box 12)
        - Galveston, Texas, 9 negatives (Box 12)
        - Gambetta Monument, Paris (Box 12)
        - Garden of the Gods (Colorado), 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Georgia
          - Atlanta, 2 negatives (Box 12)
          - Savannah River (Box 12)
        - Gordins (nematode): cross section (Box 12)
        - Grand Canyon, Colorado (Box 12)
        - Great Salt Lake, Utah (Box 12)
        - Greenhouse at the University of Michigan Botanical Gardens with Snake Pits (Box 12)
        - Grosse, E. M.
          - Photographing wheat (Box 12)
          - Portrait (Box 12)
        - Grosse, Sydney grave (Box 12)
        - Gypsy Moth Spraying
          - Forest (Box 12)
          - Brush scorched by kerosene torch, 2 negatives (Box 12)
          - Kerosene torch (Box 12)
          - Machine (front), 3 negatives (Box 12)
          - Machine (top) (Box 12)
          - Side view (Box 12)
        - Haines Houser Machine: Merced, California, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Hansel, Mr., 3 negatives (Box 12)
        - Harpers Ferry, Virginia (Box 12)
        - Haswell, Mr., 3 negatives (Box 12)
        - Hawaiian Sugar Planters' Association (HSPA)
          - Barn (Box 12)
          - Cane wagons, 2 negatives (Box 12)
          - Chemical lab, 2 negatives (Box 12)
          - Ewa Sugar Mill (Box 12)
          - Main building (Experiment Station) (Box 12)
          - Pathological laboratory, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Hand (Box 12)
        - Hand shaking spores (Box 12)
        - Heldeburg Mountains (Box 12)
        - Hen and chicks (Box 12)
        - Holt Steams Draft Combine Harvester, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Homes: Kelstonleigh and Oxford Street, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Honolulu
          - Approach to, 2 negatives (Box 13)
          - Melrose Hotel (Box 13)
          - Natives (Box 13)
          - Palms, 7 negatives (Box 13)
          - Panorama, 6 negatives (Box 13)
          - Piers, 2 negatives (Box 13)
          - Street scenes, 5 negatives (Box 13)
          - Taking on pilot (Box 13)
        - Hotel Coronado, San Diego, California, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - Hotel de l'Oasis, Bishra (Box 13)
        - Houston, Texas
          - General, 6 negatives (Box 13)
          - Market (Box 13)
          - Market and fruit wagons (Box 13)
        - Hydraulic cranes: Antwerp, Belgium, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - Ibis, Australian (Box 13)
        - Idaho scenery (Box 13)
        - Iguana in Gum Tree: New South Wales, Australia (Box 13)
        - Illinois scenes (close to Chicago) (Box 13)
        - Indiana scenes (Box 13)
        - Insect (unidentified) (Box 13)
        - Insects: experiments with varying times of light exposure, 6 negatives (Box 13)
        - Iowa scenery (Box 13)
        - Irrigating date palms: Sahara desert (Box 13)
        - Kanaka huts (Box 13)
        - Kansas scenes (including grain elevators), 5 negatives (Box 13)
        - Korsör, Denmark (Box 13)
        - Kuring-gai
          (Cobb family residence in New South Wales, Australia)
          - Back corner (Box 13)
          - Back view (Box 13)
          - Bath (Box 13)
          - Children's room (Box 13)
          - Dining room (Box 13)
          - Drawing room, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Exterior (Box 13)
          - Front, exterior view (Box 13)
          - Front corner (Box 13)
          - Front door (Box 13)
          - Front hall, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Gallery, 4 negatives (Box 13)
          - Great room (Box 13)
          - Hall, 4 negatives (Box 13)
          - Laboratory, 2 negatives (Box 13)
          - Mamma's room (Box 13)
          - Margaret's room, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Parlor (Box 13)
          - Shop, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Sitting room (Box 13)
          - Sleeping room (Margaret and Mamma) (Box 13)
          - Study, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Upper hall, 3 negatives (Box 13)
          - Veranda (Box 13)
          - Victor's room (Box 13)
          - View outside from rear room (Box 13)
        - Lake Pend d'Oreille and Clark's Fork River, Idaho (Box 13)
        - Lambrigg
          (residence and farm of William Farrer)
          - Planting wheat (Box 13)
          - Sowing wheat (Box 13)
        - Laramie, Wyoming (state university in background) (Box 13)
        - Lavender Bay, North Sydney, New South Wales, Australia, 6 negatives (Box 13)
        - Lawson, New South Wales, Australia
          - General views, 4 negatives (Box 13)
          - Gum trees (Box 13)
        - Lecture hall and chemistry lab: Berlin, Germany, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - Leigh (John) house: Compton, California (Box 13)
        - Lively excursion: Galveston, Texas, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - Liverpool, England: ship elevators (Box 13)
        - London, England, 5 negatives (Box 14)
        - Los Angeles, California
          - General (Box 14)
          - Oil wells, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Lowrie and McLean, Messrs. (Box 14)
        - Mandarin orange (diseased) (Box 14)
        - Manitou Springs, Colorado, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Mansfield, Ohio (Box 14)
        - Marseilles to Lyon (France), 3 negatives (Box 14)
        - McAlpine, Mr. (Box 14)
        - McAlpine and Farrer, Messrs. (Box 14)
        - McAlpine, Farrar, and Shelton, Messrs. (Box 14)
        - Malvern, Arkansas (Box 14)
        - Martin, Mr. (Box 14)
        - Medicine dropper (Box 14)
        - Melbourne, Victoria, Australia: Coffee Palace (Box 14)
        - Merced, California (Box 14)
        - Minneapolis, Minnesota (Box 14)
        - Mission interior, San Antonio (Box 14)
        - Molyeux, Mr. (Box 14)
        - Montana scenes (Box 14)
        - Monterey Cypress (Box 14)
        - Moss pedicel, cross section (Box 14)
        - Moss Vale, New South Wales, Australia
          - General view (Box 14)
          - Railway station (Box 14)
        - Mount Lowe (in southern California)
          - Observatory (Box 14)
          - Railway (Box 14)
          - Sierra Madre Mountains (Box 14)
        - Mountains (Australia)
          - Between Brisbane and Toowoomba (Box 14)
          - Near Toowoomba (Box 14)
        - Narromine (Bragg's siding), New South Wales, Australia (Box 14)
        - Native companion (bird, Australia) (Box 14)
        - New Orleans, Louisiana
          - Canal Street and levee (Box 14)
          - River Boat & levee (Box 14)
          - Street scenes (Box 14)
        - Niagara Falls and Kentucky farm (Box 14)
          (2 images on one plate)
        - Normandy, France: old church (Box 14)
        - North Sydney
          - Bowling green (Box 14)
          - Ridge Street (Box 14)
        - Northern Colorado irrigation land between Eton and Greeley (Box 14)
        - Oakland, California: piers, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Ogden, Utah (Box 14)
        - Ohio
          - Oil Tanks (Box 14)
          - Railway Stations (Box 14)
          - Typical Scenes (Box 14)
        - Oklahoma scenes (Box 14)
        - Oklawaha River, Florida, 5 negatives (Box 14)
        - Orange orchard between Brisbane, Queensland and Tweed Heads, New South Wales (Box 14)
        - Oregon scenes (including the Williamette River and Table Rock) (Box 14)
        - Pandamus, Queensland, Australia, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Paterson Glacier (Spokane, Washington) (Box 14)
        - Pen and ink drawings (images from newspapers and other publications), 8 negatives (Box 14)
        - Pennsylvania scene (Box 14)
        - Pigs (young Berkshire) (Box 14)
        - Pike's Peak, Colorado, 4 negatives (Box 14)
        - Pike's Peak Railway, 4 negatives (Box 14)
        - Pineapple plantation (probably Hawaii) (Box 14)
        - Poor farm (unidentified locale) (Box 14)
        - Portland, Oregon (Box 14)
        - Proctor family grave monuments, 3 negatives (Box 14)
        - Proctor family homestead (unidentified location, probably Massachusetts), 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Proctor family place (Spencer, Massachusetts), 4 negatives (Box 14)
        - Prouty family place, Spencer, MA (Box 14)
        - Puget Sound, Washington (Box 14)
        - Pymble, New South Wales, Australia
          - General views, 10 negatives (Box 14)
          - Railway station (Box 14)
          - Wire gate (Box 14)
          - Wire fence (Box 14)
        - Queensland, Australia homestead (between Brisbane and Toowoomba) (Box 14)
        - Queenstown, Ireland, 3 negatives (Box 14)
        - "Quinsig" (possibly Lake Quinsigamond near Worcester, Massachusetts) (Box 14)
        - Rhine River, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Rhone River, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - River scenes (unidentified) (Box 14)
        - Rocky Mountains, summit (Box 14)
        - Routes in the United States and Europe, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Sagebrush (Box 14)
        - Sahara (entrance to) (Box 14)
        - St. John's River, Florida (Box 14)
        - St. Lawrence River to Massachusetts (Box 14)
        - St. Lawrence to Fort Worth, Texas, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - St. Louis, Missouri to Fort Worth, Texas, 5 negatives (Box 14)
          (includes images of people and a train wreck on journey between two cities)
        - St. Paul, Minnesota (includes grain elevators in Minneapolis) (Box 15)
        - Salt Lake City, Utah
          - General (Box 15)
          - Great Salt Lake (Box 15)
          - Main Street (Box 15)
          - Salt Lake City and northern Sahara (Africa) (Box 15)
          - Salt work (Box 15)
        - Samoa
          - Apia, 8 negatives (Box 15)
          - Outlying islands (Box 15)
          - Palms and breadfruit (Box 15)
          - Samoans in canoes, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Street scenes, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Upola, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - San Antonio, Texas (Box 15)
        - San Francisco, California
          - General (Box 15)
          - Cliff House, 5 negatives (Box 15)
          - Japanese Garden (Box 15)
          - Market Street, 6 negatives (Box 15)
          - Near foot of Market Street, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Pilot Schooner No. 7 (Box 15)
          - Regiment of volunteers (Box 15)
          - Seal rocks, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Street scenes (Box 15)
          - Sutro Heights, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - United States Army volunteers, marching (Box 15)
        - San Joaquin River, California (Box 15)
        - Sawing stove wood (New South Wales, Australia) (Box 15)
        - Scenery near Mount Shasta, California (Box 15)
        - Sea gulls, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Shasta Springs, California (Box 15)
        - Sheep (Australia) (Box 15)
        - Sheep dung sieve (Box 15)
        - Shelton, E. M.
          - Children (Box 15)
          - Residence (probably in Queensland, Australia), 4 negatives (Box 15)
          - Residence (Seattle, Washington) (Box 15)
        - Ship elevators: Antwerp, Belgium, 7 negatives (Box 15)
        - Shutter Timer, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Sierra Madre Mountains, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Sierra Nevadas, coach, 4 negatives (Box 15)
        - Sieve for Spores (Box 15)
        - Siskiov, Oregon (Box 15)
        - Snow (John) house, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - South Carolina
          - Cotton Fields (Box 15)
          - Pine Ridge (Box 15)
          - Typical roads, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Woodlands (Box 15)
        - Spencer, Massachusetts and environs
          - General, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Hillsville (Box 15)
          - Wire Village
            - General, 3 negatives (Box 15)
            - House, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - Panorama, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Splitting a wheat grain (Box 15)
        - State Road, Massachusetts
          - Crusher (machinery), 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Last layer of road, 4 negatives (Box 15)
          - Placing the first layer (metal) (Box 15)
        - S.S. Manuka, 7 negatives (Box 15)
        - S. S. Moana
          - Auckland, New Zealand (Box 15)
          - Deck (near Auckland, New Zealand) (Box 15)
          - Deck view (Box 15)
          - Getting Up Sails (San Francisco, California) (Box 15)
          - Hoisting Sail (San Francisco, California) (Box 15)
          - Stern deck (Box 15)
        - S.S. Moldavia and S.S. Orotava, 4 negatives (Box 15)
        - S.S. Tacoma (crossing the Columbia River from Goble, Oregon to Kalama, Washington), 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - S.S. Topeka, group of passengers from (Box 15)
        - Steer roping contest: Fort Worth, Texas, 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Stockton, California (Box 16)
        - Sugarmills and sugar beet processing: Salinas, California (Box 16)
        - Swedish Farmhouse: Alnarps, Sweden (Box 16)
        - Sweetwater Dam (San Diego, California) and Tijuana, Mexico, 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Swine: Alnarp, Sweden (Box 16)
        - Sydney, New South Wales, Australia
          - General, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Brickfield Hill (Box 16)
          - Circular Quay, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Custom House (Box 16)
          - Darling Harbor, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - George St. (Box 16)
          - Harbor
            - General, 2 negatives (Box 16)
            - Rowboat (Box 16)
            - Sail boats, 3 negatives (Box 16)
            - Ship and tug (Box 16)
          - Kerosene Bay (Box 16)
          - King St., 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Land's Building, 3 negatives (Box 16)
          - McMahon's Point, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - McQuarrie St (Box 16)
          - Milson's Point, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - North German Lloyd Steamer (Box 16)
          - Prince Alfred Hospital (Box 16)
          - Watering Cart (Box 16)
        - Tacoma, Washington
          - General, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Balloon, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Coal Elevator (Box 16)
          - Wharf (Box 16)
        - Tapeworm hooklets (hands illustrating way of working), 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Tennessee, 6 negatives (Box 16)
        - Tent (Box 16)
        - Texas (Box 16)
        - Thompson and McAlpine, Messrs. (Box 16)
        - Tree (locale unknown, possibly the Bahamas) (Box 16)
        - Trolley: Antwerp, Belgium (Box 16)
        - Troy, New York (Box 16)
        - Troy and Johnsonville, New York (Box 16)
        - Tucker Residence, North Brookfield, Massachusetts
          - Views of house, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Group portrait: Tucker and Cobb families, 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Tuilleries, Paris, 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Tweed Heads, New South Wales, Australia
          - General, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - First train arrival, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Screw pine, 3 negatives (Box 16)
        - Villa Hildisch, 4 negatives (Box 16)
        - Wagga Wagga Experimental Farm, New South Wales, Australia
          - General, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Disc Harrow (Box 16)
          - "Estella" (Coleman's House), 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Grubbing stumps (Box 16)
          - Gum tree (Box 16)
          - Laboratory, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Laboratory roof, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Lucerne cultivating (Box 16)
          - Priddy (woman) (Box 16)
          - Spading harrow, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Two-horse cultivator (Box 16)
          - View from laboratory, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Wheat sowing (Box 16)
        - Wagon Train, (wheat being weighed): California (Box 17)
        - Wallaby, dead (Box 17)
        - Warwick, Massachusetts
          - Scenes, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Tyler place (Box 17)
        - Warwick Plains, Queensland, Australia
          - General (Box 17)
          - Typical homestead (Box 17)
          - Typical land (grass tree) (Box 17)
        - Washington state scene (?) (Box 17)
        - Washington, D. C: Capitol Building, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - Watson family place (Box 17)
        - Wheat grading sieves, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - Wheat grain (cross section) (Box 17)
        - Whitelegge, Mr., 2 negatives (Box 17)
        - Willamette River, Oregon (Box 17)
        - Wisconsin (unidentified scene) (Box 17)
        - Wolangar Experimental Station, Queensland, Australia, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - Woods Hole, Massachusetts
          - General, 4 negatives (Box 17)
          - Fish Commission laboratory, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Laboratories (Box 17)
        - Worcester, Massachusetts and environs
          - Boynton, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Snowbanks: Worcester Common, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Front Street (Box 17)
          - Gates Hill, 5 negatives (Box 17)
          - Horse Trotting (Box 17)
          - Lancaster (Box 17)
          - Main St. (Box 17)
          - 30 Maynard Street, 11 negatives (Box 17)
            (Cobb family residence during N. A. Cobb's Special Commission to the United States, 1898-1901)
          - Maywood Street, 6 negatives (Box 17)
          - Merrick Street, 3 negatives (Box 17)
          - Piedmont Church (Box 17)
          - Prescott Street (Box 17)
          - Sky Shutter, 3 negatives (Box 17)
          - Snow & Ice, 32 negatives (Box 17)
          - Street scenes, 5 negatives (Box 17)
          - Worcester Polytechnic Institute (Box 17)
        - Wyoming: snow ferries and typical basin (Box 17)
        - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming
          - General (Box 17)
          - Beaver dam and Mammoth Springs (Box 17)
          - El Capitan (Box 17)